<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>My Cool Site</title><link href="https://Head8che.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://Head8che.github.io/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://Head8che.github.io/</id><updated>2021-10-06T02:00:00-07:00</updated><entry><title>Finding Neemo</title><link href="https://Head8che.github.io/finding-neemo.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-10-06T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-10-06T02:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Danger Doggo</name></author><id>tag:head8che.github.io,2021-10-06:/finding-neemo.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"I Promise, I Will Never Let Anything Happen To You...Nemo."
&lt;span style='font-size:100px;'&gt;&amp;#128044;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just keep swimming.” This classic line from one of our favorite (albeit forgetful) fish friends has gotten us all through bad days aplenty. Ellen DeGeneres delivers a one-of-a-kind performance as Dory in Finding Nemo and the aptly-named sequel, Finding …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;"I Promise, I Will Never Let Anything Happen To You...Nemo."
&lt;span style='font-size:100px;'&gt;&amp;#128044;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just keep swimming.” This classic line from one of our favorite (albeit forgetful) fish friends has gotten us all through bad days aplenty. Ellen DeGeneres delivers a one-of-a-kind performance as Dory in Finding Nemo and the aptly-named sequel, Finding Dory. A dynamic duo, these two movies top our list for Friday night movies with the kids. But, c’mon, sometimes you just can’t wait till the weekend. If you need a little mid-week mood boost but don’t have time for a double-feature, we’ve got three words for you: Finding Nemo quotes. Because it’s always a good time to revisit some of the best lines from the cutest lucky-finned clownfish ever (AKA Nemo), along with Marlin, Dory, Crush, and the whole underwater gang.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Lion King</title><link href="https://Head8che.github.io/lion-king.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-09-07T01:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-09-07T01:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Danger Doggo</name></author><id>tag:head8che.github.io,2021-09-07:/lion-king.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hakuna Matata.
&lt;span style='font-size:100px;'&gt;&amp;#129409;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As one of 2019’s most talked-about movies, Disney’s The Lion King was revived through a CGI remake last summer. Whether you’re a fan of the all-star remake or not, the 1994 classic continues to have a hold over our hearts (which is why we’re …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hakuna Matata.
&lt;span style='font-size:100px;'&gt;&amp;#129409;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As one of 2019’s most talked-about movies, Disney’s The Lion King was revived through a CGI remake last summer. Whether you’re a fan of the all-star remake or not, the 1994 classic continues to have a hold over our hearts (which is why we’re stoked we can watch both versions on Disney+). There are lessons to be learned – by both kids and adults! – about love, leadership, and friendship throughout the heartwarming film.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Just My First Article</title><link href="https://Head8che.github.io/just-my-first-article.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-10-08T01:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-10-08T01:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Danger Doggo</name></author><id>tag:head8che.github.io,2020-10-08:/just-my-first-article.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I like free static web hosting&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry></feed>